Laboya.
It didn't show up.
I'll do my best.
Hello, it's just me.
Hi, I'm from Nagoya. How's it going?
How are you feeling? How are you feeling? It's raining, so I'm a little disappointed.
I've heard people saying, "What should we do?" It's raining today, but I'm sure the audience will be excited, so please enjoy the show.
I'm sorry, I don't have any color on my lips.
You're so cute!
Peralin's father's survey team
Well, here we are!
It's time for Rinaldi's local love, just in time.
Yay!
Rehearsal is over.
What do you think?
Isn't she looking good?
I'm wearing twin-tails today.
So cute!
I'm wearing twin-tails.
I'm going to eat the Bowling Pawn Mabushi, the winner's prize, and then I'm going to eat it.
Bowling quality fistful?
I'm going to eat the quality fist and do my best!
Today.
So...
Listen to me.
I don't have a barker.
I'm wearing my manager's barker.
My hair is half-sweating and I'm very excited about it.
Today
Rina-chan's hair is tied up.
I thought it was cute.
I'm going to do my best today.
Here's a shot of Rina.
She's going to do her best.
Please take a picture.
I'm wearing my rehearsal barker.
I've been told that you like my hair.
I didn't say that.
You didn't?
That's how I felt.
I could tell.
I'm sure we'll both do our best.
I look forward to working with you.
Bye-bye for now.
Bye-bye bye-bye Ron
It's one hour before the show.
Usually
Before the show.
I change half an hour before the show.
You're early.
You're talking fast.
You feeling good?
What's the point today?
I dyed my hair.
I'm going to do my bangs here.
But I'm not used to it yet.
I'm not used to it.
But today is good.
It looks good.
It's so beautiful.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'll do my best.
Bye-bye.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you for your hard workThank you for your hard work
Bye bye.
What did you think of today?
I'm going to cut that out.
Well, you know...
I came to Nagoya.
It's been a year since I've been here.
It was a lot of fun again.
It was a lot of fun.
You know...
You're pointing it at the camera.
Oh, no, no, no!
Shut up!
It's just that there's no excitement.
Uru-chan
fought with Mr. Rinshu at the turn.
They always fight there, don't they?
I won't tell you where in the spinning circle, but there is a place where I fight with Mr. Rinsch.
That's right.
I thought I could fight.
I thought we had a fight.
It wasn't joking around, it was a fight.
It wasn't joking around.
It was a fight. What do you think, Limey?
I do, but, you know...
When that scene came, Lurie looked like he was really serious. I thought, "I have to be serious about this.
I really had to go for it. Oh, it hurt. It was painful.
It was at the time of Mon. Where was it? At the Mon.
Talyl, you know, Talyl is, you know, she's, you know, she's amazing, you know. He's already this far.
I won't say where, I won't say where, but he's already gone this far. He's going this far. He's doing it with such vigor.
He's doing it.
I'm coming in. Oh, yes.
Which one did you think was better?
I didn't think so at all.
I'm sorry.
That's what I thought.
Bye-bye.
We're done.
How was your day? Today.
It was good.
She said it was good.
See you next time in Osaka.
Mom's not here.
Bye bye.
He's so cute.
He's a little jumpy, but that's okay.
He's got a lot of hair.
My antennae are up, but...
How was your day?
Thank you, mother and son.
Hey, you were in charge.You were in charge, right?
It was a little... embarrassing.
Which one?
Disappeared.
The first one.
It was embarrassing to hear it.
It's always played at rehearsals.
But it didn't play this time, did it?
Sure, sure, sure.
Got it!
Now that you mention it...
I'm a little embarrassed.
It's just some fans...
It's like... it's not Risa-chan next time.
I saw a mysterious look on their faces.
I thought, "Oh, she's right!
I got it!
Congratulations!
It was fun. I loved Hase Park.
It was nice.
It was... it was... it was... it was... it was...
It was fun.
Thank you very much.
She wore a ponytail today.
She's so cute.
You too, Risa.
Oh, me too.
I don't know if you're taking pictures.
Thank you very much.
Shall I take a picture for you?